Guide to the Stanford University Website Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Schools, 2010-2011; Series 2
  - Humanities and Sciences, 2010-2012
    - English, Department of, 2011-2013; engl_2011-091
      - 2012 Feb 8, english20120208; 26.5 megabyte(s) (833 files in 57 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 11, english20130211; 26.1 megabyte(s) (774 files in 33 directories)
    - Feminist Studies, Program in, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, 21.9 megabyte(s) (100 files in 59 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 13, femstudies20120313; 20.4 megabyte(s) (92 files in 58 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 4, feminist20130304; 43.6 megabyte(s) (778 files in 132 directories)
    - Financial Mathematics, Program in, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, finmath_2011-113; 54.8 megabyte(s) (125 files in 23 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 13, finmath20120313; 54.7 megabyte(s) (118 Files in 28 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 4, finmath20130304; 55.8 megabyte(s) (183 files in 47 directories)
    - History, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 4, hist_2011-092; 184 megabyte(s) (319 files in 43 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 8, history20120208; 245 megabyte(s) (353 files in 43 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 14, history20130214; 30.5 megabyte(s) (714 files in 168 directories)
    - History and Philosophy of Science and Technology, Program in, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 25, hpst20120725; 107 megabyte(s) (349 files in 18 directories)
    - Human Biology, Program in, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, humbio_2011-118; 21.7 megabyte(s) (109 files in 8 directories)
      - 2012 March 12, humbio20120312; 549 megabyte(s) (2839 files in 185 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 6, humbio20130306; 588 megabyte(s) (3061 files in 155 directories)
    - International, Comparative, and Area Studies, Division of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 May 11-17, ica_2011-114; 905 megabyte(s) (5324 files in 448 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 13, ica20120313; 958 megabyte(s) (9375 files in 3817 directories)
      - Center for African Studies, 2012
        - 2012 March 28, african20120328; 53.7 megabyte(s) (114 files in 40 directories)
      - Ho Center for Buddhist Studies at Stanford, 2012
        - 2012 March 28, hcbss20120328; 159 megabyte(s) (9802 files in 56 directories)
      - Center for East Asian Studies, 2012
        - 2012 March 28, ceas20120328; 150 megabyte(s) (1903 files in 36 directories)
      - France-Stanford Center for Interdisciplinary Studies, 2012-2013
        - 2012 March 29, france20120329; 288 megabyte(s) (226 files in 57 directories)
        - 2013 Mar 5, france20130305; 197 megabyte(s) (211 files in 44 directories)
      - Program in International Relations, 2012-2013
        - 2012 March 28, intrel20120328; 7.97 megabyte(s) (108 files in 34 directories)
        - 2013 Mar 5, internationalrelations20130305; 42.4 megabyte(s) (115 files in 28 directories)
      - Hamid and Christina Moghadam Program in Iranian Studies, 2012-2013
        - 2012 March 29, iran20120329; 4.75 megabyte(s) (81 files in 34 directories)
        - 2013 Mar 5, iranian20130305; 6.86 megabyte(s) (59 files in 28 directories)
      - Sohaib and Sara Abbasi Program in Islamic Studies, 2012
      - Center for Latin American Studies, 2011-2013
        - 2011 Aug 4, lat201108; 119 megabyte(s) (370 files in 31 directories)
        - 2012 Dec 6, las20121206; 33.7 megabyte(s) (699 files in 49 directories)
        - 2013 May 3, las20130503; 243 megabyte(s) (6661 files in 107 directories)
      - Mediterranean Studies Forum, 2012
      - Center for Russian, East European and Eurasian Studies, 2011-2013
        - 2011 Aug 30, creees201108; 468 megabyte(s) (746 files in 52 directories)
        - 2012 May 22, creees20120522; 120 megabyte(s) (631 files in 61 directories)
        - 2013 May 7, creees20130507; 92.3 megabyte(s) (428 files in 49 directories)
      - Center for South Asia, 2012-2013
        - 2012 March 29, southasia20120329; 65.8 megabyte(s) (3304 files in 125 directories)
        - 2013 Mar 5, southasia20130305; 76.2 megabyte(s) (3271 files in 129 directories)
      - Taube Center for Jewish Studies, 2011-2013
        - 2011 Aug 3, jew201108; 30.2 megabyte(s) (294 files in 40 directories)
        - 2012 Mar 29, jewish20120329; 37.2 megabyte(s) (287 files in 62 directories)
        - 2013 Mar 5, jewish20130305; 111 megabyte(s) (413 Files, 91 Folders)
      - Center for Russian, East European, and Eurasian Studies, 2012
        - 2012 May 22, creees20120522; 631 megabyte(s) (631 files in 61 directories)
    - Linguistics, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 4, ling_2011-093; 111 megabyte(s) (507 files in 160 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 8, linguistics20120208; 11.6 megabyte(s) (245 files in 144 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 11, linguistics20130211; 22.1 megabyte(s) (174 files in 130 directories)
    - Literatures, Cultures, and Languages, Division of, 2011-2013; lcl_2011-088
      - 2011 May 4, 503 megabyte(s) (10,900 files in 1198 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 8, dlcl20120208; 595 megabyte(s) (5,376 files in 1,297 folders)
      - 2013 Feb 15, dclc20130215; 814 megabyte(s) (10,750 files in 1389 directories)
    - Mathematical and Computational Science, Program in, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, 174 megabyte(s) (488 files in 48 directories)
      - 2012 March 12, mathcompsco20120312; 141 megabyte(s) (223 files in 33 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 5, mathcompsci20130305; 150 megabyte(s) (211 files in 33 directories)
    - Mathematics, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 May 6, math_2011-099; 1966.08 megabyte(s) (5629 files in 580 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 3, math20120203; 2283.52 megabyte(s) (6637 files in 633 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 13, math20130213; 3594 megabyte(s) (6851 files in 724 folders)
    - Medieval Studies, Program in, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, medi_2011-116; 0.46 megabyte(s) (46 files in 9 directories)
      - 2012 March 12, medieval20120312; 0.45 megabyte(s) (47 files in 9 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 6, medieval20130306; 0.45 megabyte(s) (47 files in 9 directories)
    - Modern Thought and Literature, Program in, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, mtl_2011-117; 27.4 megabyte(s) (750 files in 42 directories)
      - 2012 March 12, mtl20120312; 34.4 megabyte(s) (798 files in 40 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 6, mtl20130306; 34.2 megabyte(s) (582 files in 45 directories)
    - Music, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 4, music_2011-094; 15.8 megabyte(s) (378 files in 49 directories)
      - 2012 Feb, music20120208; 16.8 megabyte(s) (400 files in 51 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 11, music20130211; 12.2 megabyte(s) (362 files in 48 directories)
    - Philosophy, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 4, phil_2011-095; 132 megabyte(s) (4823 files in 49 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 7, philosophy20120207; 94.4 megabyte(s) (4030 files in 1333 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 11, philosophy20130211; 49.3 megabyte(s) (1806 files in 1165 directories)
    - Physics, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 9, phys_2011-100; 346 megabyte(s) (1496 files in 170 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 3, physics20120203; 360 megabyte(s) (1562 files in 171 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 13, physics20130213; 267 megabyte(s) (3754 files in 142 directories)
    - Political Science, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, poli_2011-105; 241 megabyte(s) (458 files in 242 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 7, political20120307; 196 megabyte(s) (2748 files in 231 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 4, polisci20130304; 193 megabyte(s) (1586 files in 237 directories)
    - Psychology, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, psych_2011-106; 206 megabyte(s) (1210 files in 147 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 22, psych20120322; 239 megabyte(s) (2464 files in 67 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 4, psychology20130304; 19.9 megabyte(s) (502 files in 51 directories)
    - Public Policy Program, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 12, pub_2011-119; 717 megabyte(s) (1262 files in 119 directories)
      - 2012 March 12, publicpolicy20120312; 993 megabyte(s) (2,422 files in 73 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 6, publicpolicy20130306; 1024 megabyte(s) (2456 files in 60 directories)
      - Stanford in Washington, 2012
        - 2012 Dec 11, siw20121211; 3.25 megabyte(s) (156 files in 23 directories)
    - Religious Studies, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 5, relig_2011-096; 1239.04 megabyte(s) (4823 files in 1257 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 7, relstud20120207; 984 megabyte(s) (386 files in 34 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 11, relstud20130211; 326 megabyte(s) (357 files in 34 directories)
    - Sociology, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, soc_2011-107; 131 megabyte(s) (258 files in 75 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 13, sociology20120313; 129 megabyte(s) (224 files in 67 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 4, sociology20130304; 47.1 megabyte(s) (208 files in 63 directories)
    - Statistics, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 9-10, stat_2011-101; 4177.92 megabyte(s)
      - 2012 Mar 1, statistics 20120301; 5775.26 megabyte(s) (11,501 files in 799 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 28, statistics20130228; 6318 megabyte(s) (10,565 files in 869 directories)
    - Science, Technology, and Society, Program in, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, sts_2011-120; 21.7 megabyte(s) (109 files in 8 directories)
      - 2012 March 12, sts20120312; 12.8 megabyte(s) (79 files in 6 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 6, sts20130306; 8.87 megabyte(s) (170 files in 34 directories)
    - Symbolic Systems Program, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 12-15, sym_2011-121; 1085 megabyte(s) (26,686 files in 8559 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 7, symsys20130307; 16.8 megabyte(s) (79 files in 70 directories)
    - Urban Studies, Program on, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 12, urb_2011-122; 62.6 megabyte(s) (147 files in 21 directories)
      - 2012 March 12, urban20120312; 104 megabyte(s) (152 files in 23 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 6, urbs20130306; 30.5 megabyte(s) (147 files in 24 directories)
  - Law, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 11, law2011-046; 2457.6 megabyte(s) (17,285 files in 11916 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 14, law20120214; 603 megabyte(s) (13854 files in 12017 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 6, law20130206; 1495 megabyte(s) (22492 files in 5559 directories)
    - Center for Internet and Society, 2012
      - 2012 Jun 7, cis20120607; 2345 megabyte(s) (10,017 files in 1,060 directories)
  - Medicine, 2010-2011
    - School of Medicine website, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 23-25, 4177.92 megabyte(s) (33088 files in 6665 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 8, med20130208; 4475 megabyte(s) (18,204 files in 2521 directories)
    - Access and Delivery of Essential Medicines Talks, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 10, adem201110; 0.67 megabyte(s) (80 files in 40 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 6, adem20121106; 0.24 megabyte(s) (18 files in 23 directories)
    - AIDS Clinical Trial Unit, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 20, actu201109; 2.82 megabyte(s) (94 files in 27 directories)
      - 2012 Jun, actu20120629; 2.86 megabyte(s) (99 files in 22 directories)
    - ALS Consortium of Epidemiologic Studies, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 10, als201110; 0.93 megabyte(s) (105 files in 26 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 6, aces20121106; 0.49 megabyte(s) (42 files in 8 directories)
    - American Parkinson Disease Association Information and Referral Center, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 10, parkinsons201110; 1.17 megabyte(s) (88 files in 22 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 28, parkinsons20121128; 4.29 megabyte(s) (70 files in 4 directories)
    - Anesthesia, Department of, 2011-2012
      - Anesthesia Informatics and Media Lab, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 15, aim201109; 11.8 megabyte(s) (144 files in 27 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 27, aim20120627; 11.9 megabyte(s) (152 files in 22 Folders)
      - Human Pain Laboratory, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 13, painlab201110; 0.49 megabyte(s) (79 files in 20 directories)
        - 2012 Dec 4, painlab20121204; 0.04 megabyte(s) (12 files in 2 directories)
      - Pain Management Center, 2011-2012
        - Systems Neuroscience and Pain Lab, 2011-2012
          - 2011 Oct 14, snapl201110; 7.97 megabyte(s) (187 files in 37 directories)
          - 2012 Dec 5, snapl20121205; 6.15 megabyte(s) (120 files in 15 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 27, paincenter20120627; 797 megabyte(s) (11,014 files in 1,044 directories)
      - Pediatric Anesthesia, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 16, pedsan201109; 26 megabyte(s) (190 files in 35 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 27, pedsana20120627; 28.9 megabyte(s) (197 files in 39 directories)
      - Neuropharmacology Laboratory, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 30, maciver20120730; 187 megabyte(s) (232 files in 15 directories)
    - Asian Liver Center, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 5-6, liver201110; 3031 megabyte(s) (1700 files in 190 directories)
      - 2012 Aug 1, liver20120801; 1853.44 megabyte(s) (1467 files in 167 directories)
    - Beckman Center for Molecular and Genetic Medicine, 2011-2013
      - 2011 Jul 6, beck201107; 1.78 megabyte(s) (115 files in 24 directories)
      - 2012 April 17, beckman20120417; (122 files in 24 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 8, beckman20130408; 1.42 megabyte(s) (48 files in 6 directories)
    - Biochemistry, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, biochem201109; 14.8 megabyte(s) (283 files in 10 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, biochem20120611; 15.7 megabyte(s) (301 files in 9 directories)
      - Brutlag Bioinformatics Group, 2011
        - 2011 Sep 15-19, dna201109; 11571.2 megabyte(s) (123 files in 15 directories)
      - Straight Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Oct 30, straight20121030; 202 megabyte(s) (153 files in 8 directories)
    - Biomedical Ethics, Center for, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 6-7, 1310 megabyte(s) (697 files in 129 directories)
      - 2012 April 17, bioethics20120417; 593 megabyte(s) (802 files in 125 directories)
    - Biomedical Informatics Program, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 10, bmi201110; 834 megabyte(s) (556 files in 235 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 28, bmi20121128; 36 megabyte(s) (256 files in 33 directories)
    - Biomedical Informatics Research, Center for, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 7-8, bmir201107; 2252.8 megabyte(s) (4733 files in 1220 directories)
      - 2012 April 17, bmir20120417; 3399.7 megabyte(s) 5,043 Files, 1,250 Folders
      - Biomedical Computation Training Program, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, biocomp201110; 0.8 megabyte(s) (87 files in 21 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 29, biocomputing20120629; 0.84 megabyte(s) (92 files in 21 directories)
    - Biosciences Programs, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 13, biosciences201110; 5.28 megabyte(s) (126 files in 23 directories)
      - 2012 Dec 4, biosciences20121204; 9.39 megabyte(s) (66 files in 12 directories)
    - Bipolar Disorders Clinic, 2011-2012; bipolar20120418; 1044.5 megabyte(s) (154 files in 49 directories)
      - 2011 Jul 8-9, bipolar201107; 1464.32 megabyte(s) (245 files in 63 directories)
      - 2012 April 18
    - Blood Center, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 11, blood201107; 578 megabyte(s) (1019 files in 166 directories)
      - 2012 April 18, blood20120418; 670 megabyte(s) (1328 files in 192 directories)
    - Canary Center for Cancer Early Detection, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 11, canary201110; 36.1 megabyte(s) (203 files in 45 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 28, canarycenter20121128; 20.7 megabyte(s) (151 files in 17 directories)
    - Cancer Biology Program, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 11, cancerbio201110; 8.02 megabyte(s) (265 files in 26 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 28, cancerbio20121128; 5.94 megabyte(s) (129 files in 30 directories)
    - Cancer Clinical Center (Cancer Institute), 2012
      - 2012 Apr 19, cancer20120419; 484 megabyte(s) (2149 files in 483 directories)
    - Cardiothoracic Surgery, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, ctsurgery201109; 19.7 megabyte(s) (330 files in 59 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, ctsurgery20120611; 237 megabyte(s) (533 files in 66 directories)
      - Adult Cardiac Surgery, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 16, adultc201109; 3.46 megabyte(s) (180 files in 34 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 27, adultcardiac20120627; 3.47 megabyte(s) (187 files in 34 Folders)
      - Pediatric Cardiac Surgery, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 16, pediatricc201109
        - 2012 Jun 27, pediatriccardiac20120627; 2.36 megabyte(s) (157 files in 34 directories)
      - Thoracic Surgery, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 16, thoratics201109; 6.19 megabyte(s) (236 files in 36 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 27, thoratic20120627; 6.35 megabyte(s) (240 files in 36 directories)
    - Cardiovascular Institute, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 10, cvi201110; 42.2 megabyte(s) (744 files in 48 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 28, cvi20120928; 48.2 megabyte(s) (706 files in 34 directories)
    - Center for Biomedical Imaging, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 11, cbis201110; 7.96 megabyte(s) (202 files in 42 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 28, cbis20121128; 9.12 megabyte(s) (162 files in 28 directories)
    - Center for Cancer Systems Biology, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 11, ccsb201110; 8.75 megabyte(s) (178 files in 41 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 28, ccsb20121128; 33.9 megabyte(s) (113 files in 10 directories)
    - Center for Clinical Immunology at Stanford, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 20, ccis201109; 186 megabyte(s) (275 files in 34 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 28, ccis20120628; 138 megabyte(s) (258 files in 34 directories)
    - Center for Education and Research in Family and Community Medicine, 2012
      - 2012 Dec 17, familymedicine20121217; 15.3 megabyte(s) (69 files in 23 directories)
      - Geriatric Education Center, 2012
        - 2012 Dec 11, sgec20121211; 178 megabyte(s) (161 files in 41 directories)
    - Center for Excellence in Pulmonary Biology, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 11, breathe201110; 2.33 megabyte(s) (171 files in 39 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 28, breathe20121128; 0.97 megabyte(s) (34 files in 11 directories)
    - Center for Immersive and Simulation-based Learning, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 11, cisl201110; 540 megabyte(s) (346 files in 70 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 29, cisl20121129; 650 megabyte(s) (425 files in 83 directories)
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Brain Sciences Research, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 4, spnl201110; 568 megabyte(s) (808 files in 70 directories)
    - Center for Memory Disorders, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 3, scmd201110; 8.2 megabyte(s) (145 files in 23 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 29, scmd20120629; 10.6 megabyte(s) (169 files in 28 directories)
    - Center for Sleep Sciences and Medicine, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 4, sleep201110; 1.59 megabyte(s) (120 files in 33 directories)
      - 2012 Aug 1, sleep20120801; 4.52 megabyte(s) (53 files in 25 directories)
    - Center of Excellence in Diversity in Medical Education, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 12, coe201110; 236 megabyte(s) (363 files in 83 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 29, coe20121129; 58.1 megabyte(s) (275 files in 54 directories)
    - Chemical and Systems Biology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, casb201109; 148 megabyte(s) (773 files in 86 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, casb20120611; 248 megabyte(s) (530 files in 66 directories)
    - Comparative Medicine, Department of, 2012
      - Veterinary Service Center, 2012
        - 2012 Nov 9, vsc20121109; 37.4 megabyte(s) (206 files in 57 directories)
    - Computational Services and Bioinformatics Facility, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Aug 8, cmgm201108; 3379.2 megabyte(s) (6004 files in 3353 directories)
      - 2012 May 14, cmgm20120514; 7025 megabyte(s) (32,827 files in 5318 directories)
    - Continuing Medical Education, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 18, cme201110; 1.79 megabyte(s) (117 files in 31 directories)
      - 2012 Dec 5, cme20121205; 3.79 megabyte(s) (86 files in 16 directories)
    - Cystic Fibrosis Center, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 12, cfc201110; 297 megabyte(s) (3335 files in 118 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 29, cfcenter20121129; 240 megabyte(s) (3238 files in 99 directories)
    - Dermatology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, derm201109; 19.4 megabyte(s) (243 files in 57 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 6, dermatology20120611; 11.1 megabyte(s) (237 files in 58 directories)
      - Program in Epithelial Biology, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 19, epibio201109; 0.94 megabyte(s) (90 files in 27 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 9, epibio20120628; 0.97 megabyte(s) (95 files in 27 directories)
    - Developmental Biology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, devbio201109; 6.25 megabyte(s) (171 files in 27 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, devbio20120611; 6.44 megabyte(s) (170 files in 28 directories)
      - Crabtree Lab, 2012; crablab20120724; 22.2 megabyte(s) (79 files in 12 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 24, crablab20120724; 22.4 megabyte(s) (79 files in 12 directories)
    - Donald E. and Delia B. Baxter Laboratory in Stem Cell Research, 2011
      - 2011 Jul 6, bax201107; 1.55 megabyte(s) (102 files in 35 directories)
      - 2012 April, baxter20120417; 1.62 megabyte(s) (102 files in 36 directories)
      - Blau Laboratory, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 24, blau20120724; 39.8 megabyte(s) (141 files in 27 directories)
    - Down Syndrome Research Center, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 3, dsrc201110; 7.19 megabyte(s) (198 files in 34 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 29, dsresearch20120629; 7.17 megabyte(s) (203 files in 34 directories)
    - Educational Programs and Services, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 17, eps201110; 1.2 megabyte(s) (80 files in 25 directories)
      - 2012 Dec 5, eps20121205; 0.31 megabyte(s) (15 files in 6 directories)
      - Office of Community Health, 2012
        - Patient Advocacy Program, 2012
          - 2012 Dec 11, ptadvocacy20121211; 144 megabyte(s) (152 files in 31 directories)
        - 2012 Dec 17, och20121217; 40.2 megabyte(s) (108 files in 13 directories)
      - Summer Research Program, 2012
        - 2012 Oct 31, ssrp20121031; 68.9 megabyte(s) (98 files in 18 directories)
    - Faculty Senate, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 17, ome201110; 0.49 megabyte(s) (76 files in 20 directories)
      - Committee on Curriculum and Academic Policy, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 17, ccap201110; 2.13 megabyte(s) (99 files in 22 directories)
        - 2012 Dec 5, ccap20121205; 0.16 megabyte(s) (18 files in 3 directories)
    - Food Allergy Program, 2012
      - 2021 Dec 11, foodallergies20121211; 2.03 megabyte(s) (50 files in 30 directories)
    - Genetics, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, genetics201109; 8.43 megabyte(s) (297 files in 50 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, genetics20120611; 528 megabyte(s) (555 files in 87 directories)
      - Helix Bioinformatics Group, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 19, helix201109
        - 2012 Jun 27, helix20120627; 1536 megabyte(s) (3710 files in 256 directories)
    - Health Improvement Program, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 18, hip201107; 250 megabyte(s) (193 files in 40 directories)
      - 2012 Oct 30, hip20121030; 150 megabyte(s) (127 files in 23 directories)
    - Health Research and Policy, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, hrp201109; 5.64 megabyte(s) (109 files in 31 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, hrp20120611; 5.63 megabyte(s) (113 files in 31 directories)
    - High-Throughput Bioscience Center, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 16-17, htbc201109; 415 megabyte(s) (355 files in 28 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 27, htbc20120627; 267 megabyte(s) (377 files in 28 directories)
    - Immunology and Rheumatology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2012 Jun 28, immunology20120628; 1.36 megabyte(s) (111 files in 29 directories)
      - Arthritis, Rheumatism, and Aging Medical Information System (ARAMIS), 2011
        - 2011 Jul 1, aramis201107; 100 megabyte(s) (249 files in 12 directories)
        - 2012 April 13, aramis20120413; 87 megabyte(s) (229 files in 12 directories)
      - Fathman Laboratory of Cellular and Molecular Immunology, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 25, fathman20120725; 276 megabyte(s) (74 files in 8 directories)
    - Institute for Immunity Transplantation and Infection, 2011-2012